[{"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Sandy Hook"]}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "WP", "VBN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 81, "question": "What to you resonates?", "question_tokens": ["What", "to", "you", "resonates", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "TO", "PRP", "VBZ", "."], "aSentId": 82, "answer": "Well, I think what happened in Sandy Hook was really a turning point.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "what", "happened", "in", "Sandy", "Hook", "was", "really", "a", "turning", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "MD", "VB", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "WP", "VBP", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 87, "question": "What do -- what do you think we can sensibly do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "--", "what", "do", "you", "think", "we", "can", "sensibly", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", ":", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 88, "answer": "I think -- I think there should be mental health for people who have mental health problems.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "--", "I", "think", "there", "should", "be", "mental", "health", "for", "people", "who", "have", "mental", "health", "problems", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 89, "question": "Better treatment, better funding?", "question_tokens": ["Better", "treatment", ",", "better", "funding", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NN", ",", "RBR", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 90, "answer": "Better treatment.", "answer_tokens": ["Better", "treatment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CD", ",", "VBG", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "POS", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "NN", "IN", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "PRP", "DT", "VBP", "TO", "PRP$", "NNS", "CC", "VB", "PRP$", "NNS", "IN", "TO", "NN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBZ", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 112, "question": "What is your reaction to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "reaction", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 113, "answer": "Well, I think as a mother of four, sending my kids out to school every day, I think that's why this tragedy affected so many people and hit home with so many people, is that we all go to our homes and send our kids off to school, and every day we assume that they're safe, and we have faith in the teachers and the school that everything is OK.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "as", "a", "mother", "of", "four", ",", "sending", "my", "kids", "out", "to", "school", "every", "day", ",", "I", "think", "that", "'s", "why", "this", "tragedy", "affected", "so", "many", "people", "and", "hit", "home", "with", "so", "many", "people", ",", "is", "that", "we", "all", "go", "to", "our", "homes", "and", "send", "our", "kids", "off", "to", "school", ",", "and", "every", "day", "we", "assume", "that", "they", "'re", "safe", ",", "and", "we", "have", "faith", "in", "the", "teachers", "and", "the", "school", "that", "everything", "is", "OK", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "RBR", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "WDT", ":", "RB", "IN", "NN", "RBR", "VBP", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 129, "question": "What is your view?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "view", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 130, "answer": "I mean, we just need better enforcement of the laws that -- first of foremost better are already put in place.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "mean", ",", "we", "just", "need", "better", "enforcement", "of", "the", "laws", "that", "--", "first", "of", "foremost", "better", "are", "already", "put", "in", "place", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "VBN", "IN", "JJ", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "RB", "RB", ":", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "RB", "VBG", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "IN", "VBG", "NNS", "IN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBD", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "And how do we get through that, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["And", "how", "do", "we", "get", "through", "that", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Our country is founded in such a different way that, you know, so much -- with the Second Amendment even being part of the Constitution, it's so much about protecting liberties because of how we established ourselves as a country.", "answer_tokens": ["Our", "country", "is", "founded", "in", "such", "a", "different", "way", "that", ",", "you", "know", ",", "so", "much", "--", "with", "the", "Second", "Amendment", "even", "being", "part", "of", "the", "Constitution", ",", "it", "'s", "so", "much", "about", "protecting", "liberties", "because", "of", "how", "we", "established", "ourselves", "as", "a", "country", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", ",", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "NNS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "IN", "WP", "POS", "VBG", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "How are they doing, the parents and her little sisters?", "question_tokens": ["How", "are", "they", "doing", ",", "the", "parents", "and", "her", "little", "sisters", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", ",", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "PRP$", "JJ", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "You know, time, I think, creates this stark realization of what's missing in your life.", "answer_tokens": ["You", "know", ",", "time", ",", "I", "think", ",", "creates", "this", "stark", "realization", "of", "what", "'s", "missing", "in", "your", "life", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "RB", "VBG", "WP", "PRP", ":", "PRP$", "NN", "VBZ", "."], "qSentId": 214, "question": "Why is that the solution?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "that", "the", "solution", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 215, "answer": "Well, Piers, I don't think you're quite accurately stating what I -- my job is.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "Piers", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "you", "'re", "quite", "accurately", "stating", "what", "I", "--", "my", "job", "is", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "IN", "DT", ",", "NNS", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 264, "question": "What is your answer for that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "answer", "for", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 265, "answer": "Well, first of all, guns are prohibited in the airplane.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", "of", "all", ",", "guns", "are", "prohibited", "in", "the", "airplane", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "RB", "DT", "VBN", ",", "VBN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 287, "question": "How do you kind of regulate that?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "kind", "of", "regulate", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 288, "answer": "Well, certainly, you need to look beyond simply a trained, armed presence.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "certainly", ",", "you", "need", "to", "look", "beyond", "simply", "a", "trained", ",", "armed", "presence", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 304, "question": "What weapon will you give your trained security people?", "question_tokens": ["What", "weapon", "will", "you", "give", "your", "trained", "security", "people", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "IN", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP$", "VBN", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 305, "answer": "We'll give them what they need to get to do the job to protect the children.", "answer_tokens": ["We", "'ll", "give", "them", "what", "they", "need", "to", "get", "to", "do", "the", "job", "to", "protect", "the", "children", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "RB", ":", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", ":", "DT", "NNS", ",", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "NNS", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "WP", "VBZ", "DT", "JJS", "NN", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 309, "question": "So just to -- just to clarify, would you give them AR- 15s?", "question_tokens": ["So", "just", "to", "--", "just", "to", "clarify", ",", "would", "you", "give", "them", "AR-", "15s", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "RB", "TO", ":", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "-NONE-", "CD", "."], "aSentId": 310, "answer": "This is not -- this is the -- the experts, the school safety experts, the national law enforcement people, they will recommend what is the best way to protect the children in this environment.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "is", "not", "--", "this", "is", "the", "--", "the", "experts", ",", "the", "school", "safety", "experts", ",", "the", "national", "law", "enforcement", "people", ",", "they", "will", "recommend", "what", "is", "the", "best", "way", "to", "protect", "the", "children", "in", "this", "environment", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "."], "qSentId": 311, "question": "What would you do?", "question_tokens": ["What", "would", "you", "do", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 312, "answer": "I would give them a weapon so they could take the shooter out.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "would", "give", "them", "a", "weapon", "so", "they", "could", "take", "the", "shooter", "out", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 318, "question": "So I'm asking you again, just to clarify, would you give these trained people you're going to train up AR-15 assault rifles?", "question_tokens": ["So", "I", "'m", "asking", "you", "again", ",", "just", "to", "clarify", ",", "would", "you", "give", "these", "trained", "people", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "train", "up", "AR-15", "assault", "rifles", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "PRP", "RB", ",", "RB", "TO", "VB", ",", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "VBN", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "RP", "-NONE-", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 319, "answer": "I disagree with your point.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "disagree", "with", "your", "point", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Congress", "Columbine"]}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "IN", "NNP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", "RB", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CC", "RB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 328, "question": "But just very quickly, you don't think removing AR-15s would help safety?", "question_tokens": ["But", "just", "very", "quickly", ",", "you", "do", "n't", "think", "removing", "AR-15s", "would", "help", "safety", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "RB", "RB", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "VBG", "NNS", "MD", "VB", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 329, "answer": "I think that Congress could pass a half a dozen laws just like they did with the ban on Columbine, and yet the tragedy occurred.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "that", "Congress", "could", "pass", "a", "half", "a", "dozen", "laws", "just", "like", "they", "did", "with", "the", "ban", "on", "Columbine", ",", "and", "yet", "the", "tragedy", "occurred", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "JJ", "IN", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "."], "qSentId": 343, "question": "What do you think of it?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "of", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 344, "answer": "Well, first, I have to say I'm thankful that you keep this dialogue going.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "first", ",", "I", "have", "to", "say", "I", "'m", "thankful", "that", "you", "keep", "this", "dialogue", "going", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "PRP", "RB", "RB", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 349, "question": "Is that the way you're going to make a Sandy Hook stop and just say, we'll just sell, what, hundreds of thousands of more guns and put armed guards in every school in America?", "question_tokens": ["Is", "that", "the", "way", "you", "'re", "going", "to", "make", "a", "Sandy", "Hook", "stop", "and", "just", "say", ",", "we", "'ll", "just", "sell", ",", "what", ",", "hundreds", "of", "thousands", "of", "more", "guns", "and", "put", "armed", "guards", "in", "every", "school", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NN", "CC", "RB", "VBP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ",", "WDT", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "JJR", "NNS", "CC", "VBD", "VBN", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 350, "answer": "I thought the president had it absolutely right today.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "the", "president", "had", "it", "absolutely", "right", "today", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 361, "question": "When people say to you, John, as they say to me, you're anti-the Constitution, you're anti-the Second Amendment, I'm entitled to all these assault weapons, what do you say?", "question_tokens": ["When", "people", "say", "to", "you", ",", "John", ",", "as", "they", "say", "to", "me", ",", "you", "'re", "anti-the", "Constitution", ",", "you", "'re", "anti-the", "Second", "Amendment", ",", "I", "'m", "entitled", "to", "all", "these", "assault", "weapons", ",", "what", "do", "you", "say", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "NNS", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "TO", "DT", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 362, "answer": "I'm a gun owner.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "a", "gun", "owner", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["John"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "TO", "RB", "VBN", "TO", "PRP$", "NN", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 420, "question": "What are you looking for?", "question_tokens": ["What", "are", "you", "looking", "for", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VBG", "IN", "."], "aSentId": 421, "answer": "They need to personally come to my house, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["They", "need", "to", "personally", "come", "to", "my", "house", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 433, "question": "Nobody called, nobody rang?", "question_tokens": ["Nobody", "called", ",", "nobody", "rang", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "VBD", ",", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 434, "answer": "OWE: It was sad.", "answer_tokens": ["OWE", ":", "It", "was", "sad", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", ":", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJR", "."], "qSentId": 436, "question": "What did you make of the race, in the end?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "you", "make", "of", "the", "race", ",", "in", "the", "end", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 437, "answer": "I was -- I was really surprised that it wasn't closer.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "was", "--", "I", "was", "really", "surprised", "that", "it", "was", "n't", "closer", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "JJR", "NNS", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", ":", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "VBD", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 438, "question": "Yeah?", "question_tokens": ["Yeah", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "."], "aSentId": 439, "answer": "I can't believe that President Obama turned out bigger numbers than he thought -- than a lot of people thought he would.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "ca", "n't", "believe", "that", "President", "Obama", "turned", "out", "bigger", "numbers", "than", "he", "thought", "--", "than", "a", "lot", "of", "people", "thought", "he", "would", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBD", "IN", "PRP", ",", "JJ", "RB", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBG", ":", "VBG", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", ",", "DT", "JJ", "``", "JJ", "NNP", "''", "NN", ",", "DT", "CD", "NNS", "."], "qSentId": 443, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 444, "answer": "I thought of you, funny enough, because I was watching -- rewatching, for the third time, the entire \"West Wing\" phenomenon, all seven seasons.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "thought", "of", "you", ",", "funny", "enough", ",", "because", "I", "was", "watching", "--", "rewatching", ",", "for", "the", "third", "time", ",", "the", "entire", "``", "West", "Wing", "''", "phenomenon", ",", "all", "seven", "seasons", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "WRB", "PRP$", "NN", "VBD", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 474, "question": "Why is it so political in America?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "is", "it", "so", "political", "in", "America", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBZ", "PRP", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 475, "answer": "It's a part, I think, of how our country was formed.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "a", "part", ",", "I", "think", ",", "of", "how", "our", "country", "was", "formed", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["America"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", ":", "PRP", "VBP", "CD", "."], "qSentId": 487, "question": "How many do you have?", "question_tokens": ["How", "many", "do", "you", "have", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "JJ", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 488, "answer": "OWE: I have three.", "answer_tokens": ["OWE", ":", "I", "have", "three", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 489, "question": "What types?", "question_tokens": ["What", "types", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 490, "answer": "I don't have an assault weapon.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "have", "an", "assault", "weapon", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 491, "question": "You have handguns?", "question_tokens": ["You", "have", "handguns", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 492, "answer": "Exactly.", "answer_tokens": ["Exactly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", ":", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 532, "question": "As a gun owner, you would have no problem if President Obama said, I really want to push for these assault rifles, in particular, to be taken out of circulation?", "question_tokens": ["As", "a", "gun", "owner", ",", "you", "would", "have", "no", "problem", "if", "President", "Obama", "said", ",", "I", "really", "want", "to", "push", "for", "these", "assault", "rifles", ",", "in", "particular", ",", "to", "be", "taken", "out", "of", "circulation", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "DT", "NN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", "VBD", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "JJ", ",", "TO", "VB", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 533, "answer": "Look, I wouldn't because -- look, I like guns, and I don't own an assault rifle.", "answer_tokens": ["Look", ",", "I", "would", "n't", "because", "--", "look", ",", "I", "like", "guns", ",", "and", "I", "do", "n't", "own", "an", "assault", "rifle", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Obama"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "."], "qSentId": 537, "question": "But if they don't do that, as you point out, it's not really a ban, is it?", "question_tokens": ["But", "if", "they", "do", "n't", "do", "that", ",", "as", "you", "point", "out", ",", "it", "'s", "not", "really", "a", "ban", ",", "is", "it", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["CC", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", "DT", "NN", ",", "VBZ", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 538, "answer": "No.", "answer_tokens": ["No", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "IN", "DT", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "JJR", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "qSentId": 564, "question": "Were you as enthralled as everybody else?", "question_tokens": ["Were", "you", "as", "enthralled", "as", "everybody", "else", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "PRP", "IN", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "RB", "."], "aSentId": 565, "answer": "First of all, I probably watch more cable news than any human should be.", "answer_tokens": ["First", "of", "all", ",", "I", "probably", "watch", "more", "cable", "news", "than", "any", "human", "should", "be", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBD", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 579, "question": "Did you get to meet Jeff Ashton?", "question_tokens": ["Did", "you", "get", "to", "meet", "Jeff", "Ashton", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "VB", "NNP", "NNP", "."], "aSentId": 580, "answer": "He actually came to visit the day I did the closing argument.", "answer_tokens": ["He", "actually", "came", "to", "visit", "the", "day", "I", "did", "the", "closing", "argument", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Jeff Ashton"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["WDT", "VBD", ":"], "qSentId": 581, "question": "Really?", "question_tokens": ["Really", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "aSentId": 582, "answer": "Which was --", "answer_tokens": ["Which", "was", "--"], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "RB", "VBD", "RB", "VB", "TO", "VB", "RB", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "PRP", "DT", "``", "NN", ",", "NN", "''", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 589, "question": "What did he say to you?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "he", "say", "to", "you", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 590, "answer": "I almost didn't want to go back and see him for fear he would give me the \"oh, boy\" face.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "almost", "did", "n't", "want", "to", "go", "back", "and", "see", "him", "for", "fear", "he", "would", "give", "me", "the", "``", "oh", ",", "boy", "''", "face", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", ",", "PRP$", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 595, "question": "I want you for my Lifetime movie?", "question_tokens": ["I", "want", "you", "for", "my", "Lifetime", "movie", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "PRP$", "NNP", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 596, "answer": "I'm there, my friend.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "'m", "there", ",", "my", "friend", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["George Anthony"]}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 612, "question": "Like whom?", "question_tokens": ["Like", "whom", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "WP", "."], "aSentId": 613, "answer": "George Anthony.", "answer_tokens": ["George", "Anthony", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "JJ", "NN", "WDT", "PRP", "RB", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP$", "NN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 617, "question": "Would you have personally convicted Casey Anthony, the more you now know about the case?", "question_tokens": ["Would", "you", "have", "personally", "convicted", "Casey", "Anthony", ",", "the", "more", "you", "now", "know", "about", "the", "case", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["MD", "PRP", "VB", "RB", "VBN", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "DT", "RBR", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 618, "answer": "It's my personal opinion that she absolutely had something to do with her daughter's death.", "answer_tokens": ["It", "'s", "my", "personal", "opinion", "that", "she", "absolutely", "had", "something", "to", "do", "with", "her", "daughter", "'s", "death", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Casey Anthony"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Piers"]}, "docId": "130114pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "MD", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "CD", ",", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 624, "question": "Do you have any sympathy for the people that get caught up in these things?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "have", "any", "sympathy", "for", "the", "people", "that", "get", "caught", "up", "in", "these", "things", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "VBN", "RP", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 625, "answer": "This one would be a tough one, Piers.", "answer_tokens": ["This", "one", "would", "be", "a", "tough", "one", ",", "Piers", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}]